Guide to the Robert J. Leach papers, 1930-1998
Leach, Robert J. papers, 1930-1998
- Lewis K. Cook to Robert J. Leach, 1934-1953 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Josephine Crowell to Robert J. Leach, 1938-1962 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Josephine Crowell to Robert J. Leach, 1963-1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Anna Hewitt to Robert J. Leach(3/18/44 annotated), 1939-1946 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Robert J. Leach to Anna Hewitt, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Howard H. Brinton to Robert J. Leach, 1939-1954 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Anna Brinton to Robert J. Leach, 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Anna Brinton to Robert J. Leach, 1944-1969 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Robert J. Leach to Howard and Anna Brinton, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Kenneth Boulding to Robert J. Leach, 1940-1989 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Robert J. Leach to Kenneth Boulding, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Henry J. Cadbury to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1970 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Robert C. Enlish to Robert J. Leach (3/10/43 annotated), 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- J. Passmore Elkinton to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Millicent S. Foster to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Robert J. Leach to Millicent S. Foster, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- William Bacon Evans to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1950 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Bob and Margaret Blood to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1969 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Lewis Benson to Robert J. Leach, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Thyra Jane and Henry Foster to Robert J. Leach, 1942-1977 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- William Hubben to Robert J. Leach (3/30/61 letter annotated), 1943-1961 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Robert J. Leach to William Hubben, 1943, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Robert J. Leach to Henry J. Cadbury, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Andrew Bihun Jr. to Robert J. Leach, 1945-1948 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- J. Passmore and Anna Griscom Elkinton to Robert J. Leach (12/68 letter annotated), 1945-1968 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Maria Glenen (?) to Robert J. Leach (2/25/74 letter annotated), 1951-1974 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Mary Frances ("Dickie") to Robert J. Leach and family (undated letter: "Saturday"annotated), 1952-1969 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Mary K. Leach Sr. to Mary Francis, c.1953 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Mary Francis to Mary K. Leach Sr., 1953-1956 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- R.H. Francis to Robert J. Leach (3/29/68 letter annotated), 1952-1976 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Maria D. Hill ("Dixie") to Robert J. Leach (6/16/65 letter annotated), 1953-1965 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- S. Read Chatterson to Robert J. Leach, 1965-1981 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Edgar M. Gemmel to Robert J. Leach (1/20/67 letter annotated), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Robert J. Leach to Edgar M. Gemmel, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Robert J. Leach: Commonplace Book, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Robert J. Leach: Address Book, n.d. [1980s?] (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Robert J. Leach: Address Book, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Robert J. Leach: Appointment Book, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Elliot and Lillian Bryans to Robert J. Leach, 1968-1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Judy and Kurt Hillfach to Robert J. Leach and family (1/6/73 letter annotated), 1970-1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Robert J. Leach to Kurt Hillfach, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Heilberger family to Robert J. Leach and family, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Willard Heiss to Robert J. Leach, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Rachel S. Carpenter to Robert J. Leach, 1979-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- S.M. Abeynayaka ("Abey") to Robert J. Leach, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Robert J. Leach to S.M. Abeynayaka, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Margaret Bacon to Robert J. Leach, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Robert J. Leach to Margaret Bacon, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Robert J. Leach to "Cousin Charlotte", 1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1957-1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Myrtle K. Barr to Robert J. Leach, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Robert J. Leach to Myrtle K. Barr, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Robert J. Leach to Myrtle K. Barr, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- "Cousin Ruth" to Robert J. Leach, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Martha Johnson to Robert J. Leach, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Bill Jarvela to Robert J. Leach, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Bill Jarvela & Gary to Robert J. Leach, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Writings "Autumn-Winter", 1934-1954; 1934, 1939, 1944, 1949, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Volume, 1934; Fitchburg High School yearbook (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Volume, 1939; Marietta College yearbook (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Index: Correspondence, Alphabetical listing of small grouping of RJL letters to go to Kroch Library [many concerning Quakers in Nantucket Island, Massachusetts, also many personal A-L] (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Correspondence Abercrombie-Alderton, 1940-1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Correspondence Alexandre-Atkins, 1940-1995 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Correspondence Bacon-Ballou, 1940-1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Correspondence Ballou-Barton, 1946-1990 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Correspondence Bartram-Bent, 1944-1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Correspondence Bernheim-Birmingham, 1942-1995 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Correspondence Black-Boone, 1941-1994 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Correspondence Booth-Bower, 1961-1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Correspondence Bowers-Brennan, 1942-1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Correspondence Brink-Brinton, 1982-1990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Correspondence Briquet-Brown, 1941-1982 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Correspondence Browne-Burgess, 1941-1997 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Correspondence Burleigh-Byrne, 1941-1993 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Correspondence C-Carruthers, 1940-1996 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Correspondence Carsner-Chijioke, 1942-1997 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Correspondence Christian Century-Clinton, 1939-1997 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Correspondence Coates-Cohen, 1941-1994 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Correspondence Cooke-Corkran, 1935-1996 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Correspondence Corwin-Cullen, 1931-1991 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Correspondence Cunnane-Cutler, 1950-1983 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Correspondence Dann-Dekker, 1931-1984 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Correspondence Dedinsky-Dole, 1943-1996 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Correspondence Doncaster-Drury, 1943-1989 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Correspondence Duggan-Dyas, 19401992 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Correspondence Earle-Elkington, 1940-1994 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Correspondence Enquirer and Mirror-van Etten, 1943-1992 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Correspondence Etter-Evans, 1945-1997 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Correspondence F-Feder, 1952-1996 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Correspondence Feder-Felger, 1944-1997 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Correspondence Folger-Foster, 1942-1997 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Correspondence Fox-Francis, 1941-1981 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Correspondence Francis-Freeman, 1942-1997 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Correspondence Fresard-Furnas, 1944-1997 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Correspondence Gaither-Gardner, 1942-1997 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Correspondence Gardner-Gerle, 1945-1990 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Correspondence Giammanco-Gilioli, 1944-1992 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Correspondence Gilioli-Gillett, 1949-1992 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Correspondence Gloor-Gorman, 1939-1996 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Correspondence Gould-Greenhill, 1942-1995 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Correspondence Greenwood-Gutteridge, 1938-1996 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Correspondence Haas-Hall, 1942-1995 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Correspondence Hall-Hancox, 1942-1997 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Correspondence Hansen-Harvey, 1942-1993 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Correspondence Hatanayaka-Herburger, 1941-1997 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Correspondence Hesse-Hockett, 1945-1994 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Correspondence Hodges-Hough, 1940-1997 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- BOX 11 RESTRICTED - - See Archivist (Box 11)
- BOX 12 RESTRICTED (audio cassettes) - - See Archivist (Box 12)
- Photo Album "II Book B", 1918-1989; Relatives; R. L.; friends; Edgartown; South Ashburnham; Reading; South Denis; Forest Lake; Bondsville; Basil; Marietta College; (pp. 1-5) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Photo Album "II Book B", 1934-1937; Marietta College, classmates, R. L.; Washington County, West Virginia, Edgartown, Katama, Mt. Monadnock (pp.6-10) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Photo Album "II Book B", 1922-1955; R. L.; Marietta College; friends; S. Beach; N.Y. Yacht Club Ed; graduation from Marietta College; Columbus, Ohio; O'Shauggnessy Dam; Fitchburg; Olentangy Dam; Mt. Watatic; Guilford; Cleveland, Pendle Hill; Duke University; Chapel Hill; Springfield Meeting; New Garden Meeting; Camp Herman (pp. 11-15) (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Photo Album "II Book B", 1934-1985; R. L.; friends; Geneva; Bondsville;U. of Va. Charlottesville; Stillwater Meeting, Ohio; Providence Meeting; Bailey's farm near W. Chester, Penna.; Brandywine River; Bass, River; Ohio Y. M.; Barnesville School (pp. 15-20) (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Photo Album "II Book B?, 1913-1985; Friends, relatives, R. L., Frieburg, Derry, County Armagh, Stockholm, Palais de Versailles, graduation Cushing Academy; Vieux Champel, Salem College, Parc des Baux Vives (pp. 21-15) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Photo Album "II Book B?, 1917-1991; R. L.; relatives; Ticino; Italy; Chappaquiddig; Nantucket; Inglewood, Calif.; Bondsville; Social Studies Conf., E. Colint, ISA; Spain (?); Edgartown; So. Ashburnham; Eugene, Oregon; Morcins Collection; Wandsworth (pp. 26-30) (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Photo Album "II Book B?, 19-1993; R. L., friends, Morcins, Brighton, Kathmandu, Niagara Falls, Powellsville Swamp, (pp. 31-35) (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1924-1976; R. L., relatives, Marietta, Chalet Gigi, Niagara, Chautauqua, Nantucket, Geneva (pp. 1-5) (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1880-1980; Friends; relatives; Rocky River, Ohio; Lausanne Cathedral; 'Sconset; Salem; N. C.; La Jolla, Calif.; West Haven; MVJ Ry.; Hartford; Saleve; Vineyard Haven; R. L.; 1938 hurricane - Eldrooch Fish Market; Long Beach, California; 1938 hurricane - yacht club; Garden of Gods, Colorado (pp. 6-10) (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1880-1990; Edgartown; Oak Bluffs; 1938 hurricane; relatives; friends; Toledo, Spain; Smoky Mtg trip; Nantucket; Sweden; Rocky River; India - Om Krisna; R. L.; Palais de Versailles; Party - Bourg de Four; Iron Gate, Virginia; W. Virginia; Trinity College, Cambridge; Mt. Pleasant Mtg. House (pp. 11-15) (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1933-1968; Friends; relatives; R. L.; Rocky River; Paris; York; Lucerne; Lucano(?); Edgartown; Gandria; Ashburnham; Inglewood; Plymouth; Stockholm; Fire Island; Vachon Island; Hawthorne, California; Syrian Road; Concord; West Haven; 1938 hurricane; Poughkeepsie; Fontainbleu; Peabody Museum, N. Haven; Sandwich Mtg.; (pp. 16-20) (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1916-1990; Friends, Rouding, R. L., relatives, Cern, Short Creek Burial Ground, Mt. Pleasant, West Haven, Edgartown, Ashburnham, S. Ashburnham, Marietta (pp. 21-25) (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1923-1986; Friends, R. L., West Haven, Edgartown, Bondsville, Ashburnham, Vieux Champel, Saleve, Marietta, relatives, Oregon (?), Camp Herman, Stillwater,Pendle Hill (pp. 26-30) (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Photo Album "II Book C?, 1923-1990; Relatives, R. L., Edgartown, friends, Stillwater Meeting, Colora Meeting, P. H. (Pendle Hill?), Thousand Islands, Barnesville School, West Haven, Ashburnham, New Haven (pp. 31-35) (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Howe-Hyde, 1934-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Correspondence IGWE-Irwin, 1966-1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Jack?-Jean?, 1952-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Jefferson-John?, 1958-1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Johnson-Jones, 1939-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Jones-Jume, 1940-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Kahoe-Kelloway, 1945-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Kelly-Kidney, 1934-1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Kilpack, 1944-1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Kimball-Kimball Union Academy, 1947-1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Kimball-Kirk, 1957-1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Klammer-Kurson, 1942-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Correspondence LaCroix-Laughlin, 1939-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Laurie-Leach, 1938-1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Leavitt-LeVane (?), 1941-1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Levitas-Linton, 1944-1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Correspondence Lionni-Lombard, 1934-1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Correspondence Longstreth-Lyons, 1939-1997 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Correspondence "Additional list of larger correspondents up to letter 'M'", n.d. (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Correspondence Bacon, 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Correspondence Calvi, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Fager, 1988-1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Hall, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Correspondence Hansen, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Correspondence Hussey, 1983-1995 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Correspondence Jolly, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Correspondence Katzenell, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Correspondence Kauffmann, 1956-1965 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Correspondence Loebell, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Correspondence Kennioy, 1932-1949 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Correspondence Kenworthy, 1943-1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Correspondence Khim, 1984-1994 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Correspondence Koroi, 1983-1996 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Correspondence Kotschung, 1940-1966 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Correspondence Lantero, 1940-1980 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Correspondence Lawton, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Correspondence Leach, G., 1938-1965 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Correspondence Leach, W., 1947-1980 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Correspondence Legg, 1981-1994 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Correspondence Lewis, 1968-1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Correspondence Leung, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Correspondence Lindley, 1938-1944 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Correspondence Lorenz, 1935-1965 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Correspondence Lutz, 1944-1965 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Bailey, 1939-1981 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Ballou, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Bemers, 1979-1993 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Booth, 1958-1974 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Bronner, 1966-1976 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Burgess, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Cole-Baker, 1961-1993 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Coxe, 1941-1973 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Coxe, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Foster, 1941-1947 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Foster, 1947-1950 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Piers, 1986-1997 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Toek, 1983-1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Toek, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Toek, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Toek, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents Toek, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Correspondence: unindexed major correspondents (Yellig) Cromley, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Autobiography-Part I, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 64-65)
- Autobiography-Part II, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 66-67)
- Autobiography-Part III, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 68-69)
- Autobiography-Introduction, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, 1987; Book One: Father's Son (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book II, 1939-1959: Mother's Son, The American Decade, The Pendle Hill Years (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book Five: Mother's Son (Part Four), The European Decade, The Exploration of Europe Years (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book II: Mother's Son (Part Five), The European Exploration Decade, The Early Married Years (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book II: Mother's Son (VI), The European Exploration Decade, Ingants-become-children Years (Box 15, Folder 10)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book Eleven: The Children's High School Years, 1969- 1974 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
- Correspondence: Dole (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Drake (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Duff (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: "Jean" (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Correspondence: Niece Margaret (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Enander (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: Various Leach (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Fewell (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: Francis (?) (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Franks (?) (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Correspondence: "Nader" (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Hadley (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Correspondence: Great-niece Cindy (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Correspondence: Hays (?) (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Correspondence: Herrington (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Correspondence: Rich(?) (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
- Correspondence: the Jumps (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Correspondence: Khumlert (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Correspondence: Knight (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Correspondence: Powell (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Correspondence: Lee (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Correspondence: Letch (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: Henriette (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Correspondence: McManus (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Correspondence: Macphail (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Correspondence: Manners (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Correspondence: Martin (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Correspondence: Mather (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Correspondence: "Peggy" (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Correspondence: Mayhew (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 15, Folder 46-47)
- Correspondence: Meyer (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Correspondence: Miller (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 15, Folder 50-57)
- Correspondence: Pearson (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Correspondence: Peterson (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 15, Folder 60-61)
- Photographs (Box 16, Folder 1-34)
- RJL Journal, Volume 50, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- RJL Journal, Volume 51, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: "Nat" (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Aunt Jo (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Pickett (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Dandelion (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
- Correspondence: "Nat" (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Railton (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Rannet (Box 17, Folder 15-17)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: Reeves (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: Roganathan (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Rowntree (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Correspondence: Sangree (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 24-27)
- Correspondence: Krishna (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
- Correspondence: Stack (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Correspondence: Stackpole (Box 17, Folder 32-34)
- Correspondence: Various (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: Sunter (Box 17, Folder 36)
- FROM THE INNER SHORE TO THE FAR OUT ISLAND, Book Twelve: The Aquarian Revolution, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 37-38)
- Autobiography-Part IV, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 39-42)
- RJL Journal, Volume 52, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- RJL Journal, Volume 53, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Correspondence List, R-Z; Correspondences to Brenda Marston (Box 18, Folder 1A)
- Correspondence: R (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
- Correspondence: S (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 8-22)
- Correspondence: T (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 23-27)
- Correspondence: V (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Correspondence: W (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 29-42)
- Correspondence: Y (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Correspondence: Y-Z (Alphabetical) (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Pamphlets: "Historic Nantucket", "Help Wanted! The Experiences of Some Quaker Conscientious Objectors", "Friends Meeting in Geneva: History, Insights, Practice", "Students' United Nations, Geneva" (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Various American Friends publications (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Civilian Public Service information (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Records of camp, written by RJL (Box 18, Folder 48)
- RJL childhood schoolbook (Box 18, Folder 49)
- "The United States and the World War" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 50)
- "Maps" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 51)
- "Notebook" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 52)
- "Honors Paper" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 53)